(male narrator)
Previously, on a very special
Clone High:
Tempers flared,
robotic butlers cared,
saliva was shared,
and you, the audience,
were moved very, very deeply.
**
[whispering]
Trust me.
(Abandoned Pools singing)
* Way, way back in the 1980s
* Secret government employees
* Dug up famous
guys and ladies *
* And made amusing
genetic copies *
* Now the clones
are sexy teens now *
* They're going to make it
if they try *
* Loving, learning,
sharing, judging *
* Time to laugh
and shiver and cry *
* Clone High
*
All students are special
at Clone High,
but only some students
are ostracized
because they're special.
That is why it is
my great pleasure,
as president
of the student body,
to officially dedicate
this impassable moat,
protecting us from
the special ed. classroom.
[applause]
Surprised Cleopatra didn't
fill the moat with acid.
Actually, Cleo says it
would kill the piranhas.
Joan of Arc, don't think
about the moat
in terms of its
divisive ignorance,
think of it as an opportunity
for building community.
Hey, community!
Skinny-dipping in
the piranha moat!
Yow!
Everybody get
naked!
Whoo!
[splash]
Finally,
I won't be running
for re-election this year.
[voice breaking]
This is probably
the last time
I'll ever use these oversized
novelty scissors.
Unless a giant
needs a haircut.
Oh, God.
I've got to go
console her.
Abe Lincoln, don't.
She's just trying
to get attention
and you're falling for it.
Ugh, it makes me so mad
I could kiss you.
What was that
last part?
I'm sorry, what?
[stammering]
No, I said I could piss glue.
As in,
"Oh, I'm so angry
I could piss glue."
I've never
heard of that.
Well, it's a very common
expression.
Huh.
Well,
see ya.
[exhales]
Stupid, Joan.
Real stupid.
[piranhas chomping]
[plop]
[sobbing]
Oh, JFK.
I can't bear
to talk about it.
Thank God, because I
hate it when--
It all started
freshman year.
I was elected
president.
But now...
[sobbing]
Oh, JFK.
There, there.
It's term limits,
Jack.
Dirty, dirty
term limits.
[cheery]
My only hope is if someone,
and I have
no idea who,
could run for president,
win,
abolish term limits,
resign,
and endorse me as his
replacement.
But who?
Who?
Huh?
Oh, thank you, JFK.
Thank you
for your courage.
Can we make out now?
Totally.
[moaning]
Hey, Cleo.
[Cleopatra and JFK making out]
Oh.
(Principal Scudworth)
Your secret army
of clone historical figures
is maturing according
to schedule.
I'm sorry, Scudworth,
is that a scale model
behind you labeled
"Dr. Scudworth's Evil Plan"?
Say!
Where'd you get those
fresh Pumas, bro?
Actually, we're sponsored
by Puma.
These bad boys
are catalogue only.
If you're implying
that I intend
to steal the clones
away from you
and use them in an expensive
clone theme amusement park,
then shame on you.
By the by,
could I have $2 million?
[laughs]
You know...
for dry-erase markers
and such.
They've got some
keen new colors.
There's kiwi and...
mango.
For giggles, I'm going
to keep saying "no"
until you
turn the TV off.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no--
[electronic whirring]
[sighs]
Perhaps you could get
Clone High
a corporate sponsor.
Those Pumas
were rather fresh.
Sell out?
And turn the school
into an ad
for some profit-hungry
corporation?
Why, that idea's
as foolish
as getting new brakes
from anywhere but Midas.
(Joan)
I can't believe JFK
is running unopposed.
I mean, you'd think with
a school full of world leaders
someone would be into
student government.
Well, I'm a genetic duplicate
of Abe Lincoln
and I'm not fit
to be president.
If I only knew
what fears
and insecurities
were holding me back.
[slurping]
Abe, you should run.
I'll manage your campaign.
Together, we'll fight
for things that really matter,
like new bishops
for the chess club.
So what you're
saying is,
if I run for president,
I can get Cleo to like me.
That's why
she likes JFK,
because he's
a natural leader.
Great idea, Joan.
[yells]
[crash]
Clumsy, Joan.
Really clumsy.
(Scudworth)
So...
your product is called--
X-Stream Blu!
It's a power snack!
Stick it in
your face hole!
This is something
you eat?
[whispering]
It's really just pancake batter
mixed with blue house paint
in a sports bottle.
Sick!
Tight!
Cyber awesome!
I see.
Now, for allowing you
to test market
this X-Stream Blu
on my students,
I am willing to be paid
$2 million.
Allow me to confer
with my associates.
[screams]
- To the max!
- Literally!
I have low
self-esteem!
We accept
your offer.
[gasps]
Dead presidents, Mr. B.
[squeaks]
(JFK)
Ask not what
your student body president
can do for you,
ask what you can do
to your
student body president's body.
[cheering]
Okay, there's nothing
to worry about.
He's just making
empty promises
and detailing
his workout routine.
And on Fridays,
I do abs and legs,
but not calves.
As you recall,
I do those with my lats
on Wednesdays!
[cheering]
Thank you!
Good luck.
[audience cheering]
[Cleopatra and JFK
making out]
My name is Abraham Lincoln
and I'm running
for student body president.
(woman screaming)
I love you, JFK!
We've got a lot of tough issues
facing us right now,
such as adding a second section
of AP calculus
for those who have a conflict
between that class
and AP physics.
[clapping]
But first and foremost,
we must get tinted windows
for the albino wing.
[clapping]
Whoo!
Okay, you're done.
Young men and women,
please give it up for
the X-Stream Blu mega crew!
[rock music]
[audience cheering]
Hey, everyone!
I'm Tyler,
that's Paco,
and we want you to
get up out of your seats
and clap your hands
to the beat.
[clapping]
(Tyler)
'Cause we're gonna tell you
about X-Stream Blu,
a new max wicked food product
that lives where
extreme meets blue.
It comes in a totally sick
wide-mouth squeeze bottle!
[squish]
[plop]
Email!
That looks
so good!
What's in it?
Great question!
Have a t-shirt.
[boom]
That totally
answers my question!
Man, the audience
was not having that.
Huh, guys?
Um, Abe?
Just give me a few
more minutes of denial.
[banging]
Abe, Abe,
your speech wasn't
that bad.
Okay, maybe the encore
wasn't the best idea,
but the speech
itself--
Whoo!
What stinks
in here, man?
Oh yeah,
it's your campaign.
You died out there.
I mean, that assembly was like
this, boom, this!
You're the boom.
[thud]
No matter how hard I try
to live up
to the real Abe Lincoln,
I always fail.
Hey, don't worry,
man.
Your problems
are answered.
See, I met these really cool
guys after the assembly
that will so get you.
Guys, come on
in here, man!
[screams]
X-Stream Blu
in the hizz-ouse!
Flip an ollie and turn it up!
Lincoln and X-Stream Blu
will literally crunch
the googly to the max!
(all)
Hot sauce!
See, they want
to sponsor your campaign.
And all you gotta do
is abandon your values
and promote
their product
by doing some dangerous, extreme
sports-related stunts.
Just sign this legit-ass
contract!
And totally initial
article seven.
My son won't even look me
in the eye anymore!
Wait, what about
the issues, Abe?
What about the carpet
in the library?
[mocking]
Ooh, Abe's big choice.
Ooh,
I wonder what it'll be.
I'm so worried, ooh.
[TV clicks on]
[wind blowing]
[all laughing]
*
I'll never make it.
[laser zaps]
Maybe I can help,
slice dog!
Blushie!
But I'm no match
for that gang of snow sharks.
Don't worry, bro!
Blushie gonna
stream it hardcore!
[squishes]
No way!
Hop on,
extreme sports youth!
[yells]
[water crashes]
[exploding]
[women laughing]
Hey!
Let's go surf
the Internet!
What should we do
with all this X-Stream Blu?
(Abraham and Blushie)
Spray it in your face
and slam it!
[TV clicks off]
You think
it's too much?
[inhales]
(Gandhi)
Abe, I just polled everyone
in the girls' bathroom.
You're ahead!
I knew the poll--
did you say I was winning?
Straight up,
man.
Numbers don't lie.
I'm the number five.
Cleo, why are
you crying?
[sobbing]
I just don't think
things are going
to work out with JFK.
[sighs]
[whispering]
Wah-hoo.
I am so sorry.
I need someone
to comfort me.
Someone who's
leading the polls
and is named Abe.
Wait,
you're named Abe.
Aren't you,
Abe?
To the max,
Cleo.
To the max.
That's it.
All of the pictures I have of
him over my bed are coming down.
Except for that one
where he's under the tree
with his shirt off.
[moans]
We're rich, Mr. B!
Bling, bling.
But shouldn't you be saving
some of this money
for your secret plan instead
of having me gold plated
and lowered?
Don't get all up in my business,
my hydraulically outfitted
friend.
Why, I watched the first 2/3
of the MC Hammer
Behind the Music.
And if there's one thing
I've learned about money,
it's that it never runs out.
(JFK)
Hey, gay foster dads.
How do I get everyone
to like me?
Baby, a lot of people
liked the original JFK
because he was
such a caring leader
and he inspired
a generation of young people.
I thought he was
a macho womanizing stud
who conquered the moon.
[knocking on door]
Hark, that sounds
like the gentle knock
of a vulnerable teenage girl.
[door creaks]
*
You're wet.
Allow me
to dry you off...
with my pants!
I want to manage
your campaign.
Hey,
whatever you're into.
Dads,
I'm gonna be busy
nailing this kinky broad
for the next 15 minutes.
Would you shut up?
I'm here because I can't stand
Abe being Cleo's puppet
and you can't win the election
without my help.
Here's what
we're gonna do...
[inaudible whispering]
And then...
Well how about...
[inaudible whispering]
Dental dam...
[smack]
Bobby!
Okay,
no dental dam.
Folks, for my next totally
outrageous campaign stunt,
I will ride this wind surfboard,
which is connected
by a bungee cord
to this monster truck,
which my friend Gandhi
will drive back and forth
on this half-pipe,
just like the real Abe Lincoln
would've done,
had he the tools to do so.
[engine revs]
[engine roars]
[metal clangs]
[cheering]
Hey everybody,
something is on
the closed-circuit TV.
[cheering]
(announcer)
Abraham Lincoln.
Honest Abe.
Or so he'd have you believe.
Last year, Abe said
he was 15 years old.
Now he claims to be 16.
Which is it, Abe?
Better keep your story straight.
[baby cries]
He'd also like you to believe
he's not a baby eater.
But he's never gone on record
saying he isn't.
Maybe he's too busy
eating babies.
I can't wait to eat this--
[tape whines]
baby.
[all gasp]
[gags]
[slurping]
(announcer)
When is it gonna stop, Abe?
Not voting for Abe:
it just makes sense.
How did JFK get
my spaghetti video?
[dramatic music]
[whooshing]
Hey, turn that frown
upside down, Abe.
[squish]
At least it can't
get any worse.
How many times have
I told you not to say that?
Now something worse
is gonna happen,
I've seen it
on Happy Days, watch:
In three,
two,
one.
Abe.
I'm really confused about
my feelings right now.
I think I just...
need some time
to be alone...
*
with JFK.
Wait.
At least it can't
get any better.
It doesn't work
that way, Gandhi.
[fluttering]
(female singer)
* The heart in my mind
has been hoping *
*
* And the mind in my heart
has been wishing *
*
Abe?
What are you
doing here?
I come out here
to think sometimes.
Me too.
Well, right now all
I can think about
is not thinking about you over
there on your thinking dock
thinking about
what you did.
I was only trying
to help, Abe.
You don't know
what you're getting into.
What she's
getting you into.
You don't know what
you're getting into.
And that's out of
my friendship.
And you know what
hurts the most, Joan?
This nail I just
stepped on.
[ding]
But there's a metaphorical nail
in my other foot
that hurts the second most,
and it's from you
backstabbing me.
So, maybe instead of
the nail metaphor,
I should've used
a stabbing metaphor,
but it's too late for that now,
isn't it?
I guess it is.
That's where you're wrong, Joan.
Because I'm gonna win
that election
with the most
dangerous campaign stunt
since Dukakis jumped
the Snake River Canyon.
Goodbye, Joan.
[splash]
*
[intense music]
(all)
Hut, hut, hut, hut--
Hello, Clone High!
X-Stream Blu presents:
the X-Stream Blu high school
presidential debate,
with celebrity panelists
Marilyn Manson,
Mena Suvari,
and introducing
Murray T. Wayans.
[blows raspberry]
And now, he risks his ass
to thrill his class:
Abe Lincoln.
[door crashes]
[roars]
[boom]
[cheering]
[thud]
[audience cheering]
Woo-hoo!
And on this podium,
captain of the football team
and el capitán
of the fútbol team,
JFK.
Woo-hoo!
I can't see
due to the glare from
Mena Suvari's enormous forehead.
[whirring]
(Manson)
Next question is for JFK.
How do you respond
to the criticism that,
unlike Abe and myself,
you won't put yourself
at risk of physical harm
in order to gain approval?
That is a good question,
scary androgynous white guy.
And I would like to reply
by taking my shirt off.
[girls screaming]
My bare-chested opponent
raises a good point,
but he's avoiding the fact
that X-Stream Blu
is mad-packed with all nine
essential nutri-mites
to fortify your X-Zone.
(JFK)
May I respond to that?
Yes, you may.
Abe's a tot-muncher.
Oh, yeah?
For my rebuttal,
I'd like to dramatically gesture
to this giant death-defying
skateboard ramp behind me.
[metal whirring]
[fire whooshing]
[thud]
[alligators crunching]
[dolphin chatters]
I intend to ride said ramp.
Gandhi.
[groans]
You may now attach
the skateboard...
to my head.
[metal whirring]
[alligators crunching]
[dolphin chatters]
[all gasp]
[intense music]
Abe, it all
comes down to...
[slow motion]
this.
[all gasp]
[slow motion]
Gan...
dhi!
[thud]
[gurgle]
[squish]
[audience gasps]
Marilyn Manson?
Yes.
It is my professional opinion
as a rock star
and a licensed doctor,
that this student
is suffering from
malnutrition.
Mena, I'm going to need
one milligram
of sub-q glucagon, stat.
How can
this be?
*
What have I done?
Fellow students,
X-Stream Blu is a sham.
For four days straight,
Gandhi ate nothing
but pancake batter
and blue house paint.
A shallow ploy by
Racist Mammy Breakfast Foods
to jazz up an old product
with extreme marketing,
the same marketing scheme
I used to win your votes.
Well, I don't deserve
your votes.
I suck.
[audience booing]
[rock music]
[exclaims]
There goes our ghetto fabulous
lifestyle.
Bling, bling.
Wait, everyone.
You should vote for Abe,
because a real leader does
what Abe just did,
and what he always does.
He stands up for
the right thing
even if it makes him
look like a jackass.
That's the kind of jackass
I want in my corner.
[audience applauding]
That's the highest score yet
on the applause-o-meter,
the official voting system
of Clone High.
Looks like Lincoln
is your new president.
You're gonna make
a great-ass president.
Thanks, Joan,
for showing me how
to be a real-ass leader.
(man)
Hey, check out
that stray puppy.
Oh, my God,
he is so cute.
(man)
And it's licking
that dead Smurf's face.
(all)
Aww.
[crash]
Fine, whatever.
This random dog
is your new president.
Hey, new president.
That's a cute collar.
[slurping]
Well, we sure learned
a lot today.
I'll say.
But there's just one thing
I don't understand, Dr. Manson.
How does a growing boy like me
eat a healthy, balanced diet?
Well, Gandhi,
I'll tell you
the only way
I know how.
* The ancient pharaohs were not
too bright, they say *
* But they made
one contribution *
* That I live by to this day
* It's the food pyramid *
* And it's approved
by the USDA *
[upbeat music]
*
* Whole grains
are the foundation *
* So please take my advice
* Have 5 to 11 servings
of bread, cereal, or rice *
* 3 to 5 of vegetables
* And four of fruits is best
* Their antioxidants and fiber
help you to digest *
* Three servings
of yogurt, milk, and cheese *
* Will help your bones
* And subsidize
the cattle industries *
**
* A body needs to grow
* And growing takes proteins
* That's why meat
can be a tasty treat *
* Like fish or human beings
[chomps]
* When you eat your sweets
* Make sure you try
* To limit your servings
* Or you'll *
[heavy metal music]
* Die
Everybody!
[upbeat music]
* My body's a pyramid *
* That's made of healthy food *
* So do what we say
(all)
* Yeah
* Eat right every day
(all)
* Food
* I
* Love
* You
Buy American.
Well, I guess we
did learn that.
*
(announcer)
Next time, on a very special
Clone High,
someone open-mouth kisses
someone else.
So set your VCRs for stunned,
because you will be.
Oh, you will be.
(Abandoned Pools singing)
* Way, way back in the 1980s
* Secret government employees
* Dug up famous
guys and ladies *
* And made amusing
genetic copies *
* Now the clones
are sexy teens now *
* They're going to make it
if they try *
* Loving, learning,
sharing, judging *
* Time to laugh
and shiver and cry *
* Clone High